This part which was of fiber, it has completely changed
to plastic, you see
this whole diamond which was made, you guys have
seen the video of the accident, if not
go and watch it on your channel,
hey, the hand there has turned completely into ice, brother,
okay, where are you guys from,
what all things have to be done in insurance, how much time does it take,
how much money does it cost,
even after having insurance, you will live a
healthy and fun life,
brothers, and today brother, finally after 20 days
I have come to the showroom Yamaha showroom,
so let's see, sir had said that your bike is ready, so let's
see if the bike is ready or
not, how far has the bike reduced, so
let's go straight inside and show you the bike,
brother, and today I am very excited today to
buy the bike, I was missing this bike a lot,
brother, I don't know
when the bike will come, it will not come, but finally the
insurance has reduced, I have also got the bike serviced,
everything is done, so
how much will the cost of the second service be, etc., etc.,
all this will come in the next video, now let's go
inside the showroom, let's see if our
bike is ready or not, okay
So look at this, I mean we are going to the showroom brother
and let's check out the bike, the family
brother,
our machine brother, the people
set brother, and I was doing a lot of mental mixing
brother, I don't know where my brother's brother,
this one is, I
think this one looks like
my bike, I
swear brother, my brother was missing it a lot, it's been
20 days, it's been 20 days
without medicine, I just do
n't feel like doing anything, I'll take out a
taxi, I'll
meet you outside, brother, I'll show you everything brother, okay, so
brother, look, your bike is finally ready
brother, so many people are commenting to me that
brother, when there is an accident,
what all things have to be done in the insurance,
how much time it takes, how much money is spent,
even after getting the insurance,
I will tell you all the details sometime, for now, let me
check out the bike, what all stuff is fitted
in the bike brother, the one that got damaged, let's
look at the bike, this is my bike, first of all, the part
that got damaged brother,
this part of mine was damaged,
it got completely changed, it's the entire body here  There was a
scratch on it, I said
change this too, this has also been changed, this
part which was made of fiber, has completely changed to
plastic, you see this one had become
completely diamond, you people must have
seen the video of the accident, if not go and
watch it on your channel, then this had become completely diamond,
this had become completely diamond and this part
towards the handle had become completely diamond, so
this part has not come yet, this is also in the claim
and they said that plastic parts are
not included but I said brother if there is insurance then
this will also be included, you are the first owner, so they
said let's get this done too, you will have to request a little, so this
part has also come, but this will also be included,
this has completely changed, apart from that if we talk about this then
this part has completely changed
and the indicator maybe this one has changed yes this one has
changed and this mirror this one has completely changed, so the
mirror has also changed,
so overall all these parts of the bike have changed
brother, now let's talk about how much money has been
spent brother, see I have not spent even ₹1, I have spent
zero rupees, I have also received it now  I will
show it and they said just give 100 rupees
to the labour so I said come on
what all has to be done for that
brothers people did so little and you
know about the mechanic look, restless people work very hard
so I gave them 100 rupees
still I will show it to you people and it's
not a matter brother how much time will it take look brother it takes
some time it takes some time
brother it took me approx 20 days
so it definitely takes time what
according to them it seems they say it will be done
in 7 days 10 days but I have read the time taken for
parts to arrive that itself takes
some time and the rest is
not a matter of test and first and as long as it
lasts for a year maybe it is the first round
so you maybe two or three times they
say there is some time in the entire part which will be
free of cost change so this happened to me for the second time the
child dropped a small minor check so his first one
brother brother the
free service thing got over it happened for the second time now so
Maybe three times maximum I think I am
not the one who is looking for it, so that thing has been stored in me,
I will tell you for sure in the next video,
but three times
they told me that it happens, firstly, as long as you
see your bike, there is no money or charges for one year
and it takes a little time, so I apologize for that, I will have to
request you, they will do it quickly, there was
another option, if you want to get it done quickly, then
whatever part is changed,
you can give some money as security, say
Rs. 3,1500, then the goods are transported a little
quickly, transportation is done quickly,
then when all the goods are fitted in the bike,
then your money is refunded,
they do not do that, brother, they
gave me this option, but I did
not need the bike right now, I already have
only one, so I said no, let it be,
I did not have any cash money like that, so all this happens,
let me
show you the bill, the bill comes out
brother, so I will
check it out for you right away, okay
brother, look, here is the bill in front of you brother, on this  Let's
keep it, then I will tell you guys a little detail
what all I have found, so
look at the final calculation, it is written here, the
camera is clear brother, okay your brother, you are
looking at the weather a little right now, because of this there is
no sunlight, so it is taking some time to see, the
final calculation has come out, so
only for this I gave ₹100 brother, look ₹100 yes, I do
n't know what 2471 is, I thought it was the
doing amount, I just invested it
brother, look at the money here, something like this
comes in the paper, you can read everything,
okay, it does not cost much,
₹100 is yours, now if you want to give then you
can give, if you do not want to give then there is no problem, it
depends on you, you can take it for
free also, but friend, everyone has their own
thinking, there is nothing much to
say about it, otherwise all this
happened brother and when the accident happened,
I was missing my bike a lot,
after the accident, but Alhamdulillah Alhamdulillah
Bye mine is ready, there is
no need to worry, it
took me a lot of time, it took approximately 20 days for
me to get the bike
from the showroom after the accident, so hopefully you guys also have to do it properly, from now on
always
stay in gears, what happened,
and this is to meet my brothers, brother, do you
see my video, hey brother,
thank you, okay, okay, thank you so much, hey my
god, it has become a complete ice, brother, where are
you guys coming from, from Kamtoul,
okay, we just went to Kamtoul yesterday, the
time in Nepal Sky,
my house is near Dobara, so it
feels very good to meet brothers, when we
meet any of our subscribers, brother, we
cannot pay attention to it, so right now it is going on,
talk directly on the way with the front camera, directly on the bike because it is very cold, I was
also seeing the weather, how much cold is left, okay, let's do the
process, when your bike is ready, I
wish brother, all this should not happen with you,
if the treasure becomes special, then it
definitely takes this much time, brother, to make the bike
and  You will have to wait a little, you will have to put in a little effort, you will have to
request and I used to
call every day, Sir, please look into it and get
my bike repaired quickly because brother, we
cannot do anything without a bike
and especially it is not possible without a bike,
so I requested everyone a lot and they were
quite good, it depends on
what kind of service incharge is yours and
which I mean company's bike it is, it all depends on that
and
this is the whole game brother, this bike takes
so much time to arrive, sometimes it can be repaired in 10 days,
sometimes it can be repaired in seven days,
sometimes a month passes and
still the bike is not delivered, so I hope
you have got the information, if you like the
video then like, share
and definitely subscribe for your brother, don't forget to
get good blogs,
only wish you health and wish you from home and
stay, bye